# ANJALY SADASIVAN

Software Engineer

#### **ABOUT ME**

Aspirant of professional mastery calibrated with exquisite communication skills and great interactiveness. On a very simple note, I have been working with Quest Global for the past 2.2 years, in the medical domain services. Working in engineering, medical devices has always lit the passion up and has helped in sharpening the swords towards mastery. Graduating from Government Engineering College, Idukki, the urge was completing in moving forward and be a progressive learner in life. Challenges and pressure in professional life are always a privilege because ever since I have encountered them there had been an expansion of capacity, which helps look beyond the limits. The profile is all about seeking growth, and turning everything that seems hard to be little easy with progression of personal career and the growth of the organization.

C	0	N	Т	Α	C	Т

+91 9497 232 803

🔀 anjalysadasivan 18@gmail.com

• Changanassery, Kerala, India

## **EDUCATION**

## BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

Government Engineering College, Idukki

2014 - 2018 • 7.20 CGPA

Graduated with Computer Science as Major.

## SENIOR SECONDARY

*Placid Vidya Vihar, Changanassery* 2012 - 2014 • 86%

## SKILLS

С	
C++	
ASP.NET	
MVC	
.NET Core	
Testing	
Automation Scripting	

### **EXPERIENCE**

Sep 2018 - Present

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### QuEST Global

- Actively participated in developing and maintaining the software for an X-Ray Angiographic Machine.
- Worked with enhancing the features of the product and its various versions.
- Tested functionalities in both developer and real time environment.
- Enhancement of the existing software include crucial and critical tasks like enhancing the logging system of such complex working product.
- Being in healthcare domain which follows DICOM standard, a crucial feature enhancement done includes exhibition mode development for the product.
- Scripting to automate test cases using concord automation tool.
- The product includes a tablet mode operation which is completely developed on .NET platform.

Apr 2017 - Sep 2018

## **CONTENT WRITER**

## One Media InfoCreation Pvt Ltd. • Part-time

- Writing fresh and engaging contents.
- Specialised in writing content for various websites.
- Fresh and engaging articles on various topics for blogs, marketing and other purposes.
- Proficient in both English and Malayalam.
- Document creation by collecting, analyzing information from various secondary resources.

Jan 2018

#### INTERN

## UST Global

- Worked on simple blockchain projects and basic programs on R.
- Conducted research on Hashgraph and IOTA along with their deployment.

Facebook: @anjalysadasivan Skype: @anjalysadasivan LinkedIn: @anjalysadasivan